{
    "id": "1cca8a0dd1404dceb05c7c5900d4c729",
    "title": "Present Continuous Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Where …………………. you ..................... now?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is, go",
                "are, going",
                "have been, going"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................... . Don’t disturb him now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is studying",
                "are studying",
                "has been studying"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ...................... on my feet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stand",
                "am standing",
                "are standing"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Rani ..................... the plants.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is watering",
                "am watering",
                "are watering"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I .....................… to hear from them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is waiting",
                "am waiting",
                "are waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We ...................... for the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is preparing",
                "are preparing",
                "was preparing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Radha ...................... a sweater for her daughter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am knitting",
                "is knitting",
                "am knitting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahul ………………….. his homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is doing",
                "are doing",
                "am doing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ...................... for you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is waiting",
                "are waiting",
                "am waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog ..................... the cat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is chasing",
                "are chasing",
                "am chasing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Mother ..................... a cake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is baking",
                "are baking",
                "am baking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Father ..................... his bike.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is fixing",
                "am fixing",
                "are fixing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}